I teach the men I work with to learn to
become family men. Here's how you're a
family man. You decentralize yourself. I
wrote this and I don't want to talk
about it. A boy's question of the world
is what he got for me. A man's question
of the world is what's needed here. And
I teach men to show up as men and not
boys. What's needed here? Research on
happiness is I like black and white
research. If you get a gift, you're
happy. You get happier for a bit. If you
give a gift, you're even happier and
longer than if you get it. What men need
to understand is it's good for us to be
empowered, be assertive, and also to be
connected and show up and ask ourselves,
what's needed here? How do I need to
show up here? That's a man.